Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art public programs records, circa 1995-2011 COR0003.5.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Program files, financial records, and calendar productions, 1994-2011; Series 1
  - Dinner at Tosca, 2001 May 13; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Larry Rivers, 2002 May 14; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Mary Drysdale, 2002 May 15; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Jan Pottker - Janet and Jackie, 2002 May 16; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - NYC Trip - Whitney Biennial, 2002 May 17; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Julien Schnabel, 2002 May 23; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Mass Avenue Walking Tour, 2002 May 20; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Hot Mikado, 2002 May 28; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Sharon Farmer, 2002 May 29; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Night Day June 2002, 2002 June; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Flora Biddle Whitney Women Cancelled, 2002 June 3; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Lypsinka Cancelled, June 2002; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Faith Prince Cancelled, 2002 June 5; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Peter Cincotti Cancelled, 2002 June 20; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Jenny Lind Concert, 2002 June 5; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Letitia Baldridge, 2002 June 6; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Erica Hall Concert, 2002 June 8; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Loose Public Programs, 2002; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Round House Theatre, 2002 June 11; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - David Baldacci, 2002 June 12; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Rederal Reserve Lecture David Levy Ronald Abramson, 2002 June; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Did Your Mother Come From Ireland, 2002 June 18; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Nanny Diaries, 2002 June 19; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Stephen Crowley, 2002 June 25; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - NYC Fashion Tour, 2002 June 27; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - The Borromeo String Quartet, 1998; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Marcy Posen Friends, 1999 February 12; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Musical Evening Series, Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Katz T. Riley, Dawes, 1999 February 5; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - The Weilerstein Trio, 1999 May 14; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - The Angeles String Quartet, 1988 November 13; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - The Ying Quartet, 1999 April 30; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - The Takacs String Quartet, 1999 January 16; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Schidlof Quartet, 1999-2000; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Miro String Quartet Cancelled, 1999-2000; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Brentano String Quartet, 1999-2000; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Adaskin String Trio, 1999-2000; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - St. Lawrence String Quartet, 1999-2000; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Colorado Quartet, 1999-2000; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Orion Quartet, 1999-2000; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Borromeo String Quartet, 1999-2000; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Takacs String Quartet, 1999-2000; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - MES: The Brentano, 2001 October 27; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - MES: Paul Katz Trio, 2001 November 10; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - MES: The Ying, 2001 December 8; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - MES: Marcy Rosen, 2001 January 26; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - MES: The Takacs Quartet, 20001 February 9; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - MES: The Pacifica, 2001 March 16; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - MES: The Miro Quartet, 2001 April 6; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - MES: THe Cavani, 2001 May 11; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - MES Correspondence, 2000-2001; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Piano Purchase, Circa 1998-2001; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - MES Program, 2000-2001; Series 1 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Calendar December 2002, 2002 December; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - 2002 December Public Programs Calendar, 2003; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - South Pacific Panel with Molly Smith and South Pacific Performance, 2002 December; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Festive Evenign at Romania Conginal Fill Missing, 2002 December 3; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Jock Elliott - Inventing Christmas, 2002 December 4; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Fashion Trip to NYC, 2002 December 6; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Jim Leher, 2002 December 9; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - David Rockwell, 2002 December 11; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - January 2003 Public Program Calendar, 2003 January; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Israeli Concert with the Embassy, 2003 January 8; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - William Ivey Long, 2003 January 13; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Nancy Davidson, 2003 January 13; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Laboratorio de Galileo, 2003 February 18; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Galileo, 2003 January 27; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Kathryn Davis - Versailles, 2003 January 21; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - David Kahn, 2003 January 22; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Couture Accessory, 2003 January 27; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Ibero-American: Costa Rica, 2003 January 30; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - February 2003 Public Programs Calendar, 2003 February; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Degas and the Dance Trip to Philadelphia, 2003 February 15; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - May Knott, 2003 February 3; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Christopher Buckley, 2003 February 4; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Spy Dust, 2003 February 5; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Max Protetch, 2003 February 10; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Spy Museum Visit, 2003 February 12; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Robert Alexander Cancelled, 2003 February 18; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Kakakonis Book Signing with the Greek Embassy, 2003 February 20; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Lithuanian Concert, 2003 February 19; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Martha Schwartz (Landscape Series), 2003 February 25; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Barbara Corcoran, 2003 February 26; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Landscape Architecture, 2003; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Melvin Kaplan Rehearsal, 2003 February 28; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - 2003 May PPCAL FY2003, Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - May 28, 2003 FY2003 Thaddeus Phillips CANCELLED, 2003 May 28; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - May 5, 2003 Robert Massie FY2003, 2003 May 5; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - May 6, 2003 Philip Thomson, 2003 May 6; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - May 7, 2003 Paul Goldberger, 2003 May 7; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - 2/24; 4/6; 5/10 Washington Operay FY2003, 2003 February-May; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - May 12, 2003 Anne Makepeace, 2003 May 12; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - May 13, 2003 Jamees River Plantations Bus Tour, 2003 May 13; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - May 14, 2003 Bram Dijkstra, 2003 May 14; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - May 19, 2003 Joe Barber Bill Henry / The Movie Guys, 2003 May 19; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - May 20, 2003 Christo and Jeanne Claude, 2003 May 20; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - May 21, 2003 Jorg Schmeisser, 2003 May 21; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Trio Moskva Facility Rental 10/4 12/20 5/23 FY2003, 2003 May-December; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Board Tom of Grounds May 30, 2003 May 30; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Ground 4 Sculpt - Comm Board of Overseers, Circa 2003; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Marine Band - FR May 31, 03 FR, 2003 May 31; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - 2003 June PPCAL FY2003, Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - June 28, 2003 Lanford Wilson and Ari Roth CANCELED, 2003 June 28; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - June 12, 2003 Dinner at the Residence of the Ambass. of Qatar, 2003 June 12; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - June 12, 2003 Jenny Lind Concert, 2003 June 12; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - EU Contemporary Art Show June 4, 2003, 2003 June 4; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - June 10, 2003 International Court Walking Tour, 2003 June 10; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - June 20, 2003 New York Fashion Trip, 2003 June 20; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Oct 16, 2001 FY2002 Arts Mgmt w/ Michael Kaiser, 2001 October 16; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - June 18, 2003 WHNPA Panel and Exhibit Viewing, 2003 June 18; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - June 24, 2003 Richard Polsky I Bought Andy Warhol, 2003 June 24; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - June 25, 2003 Sally Martin, 2003 June 25; Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - 2003 March PPCAL FY2003, Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - March 4, 2003 Bulgaria, 2003 March 4; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - March 18, 2003 FY2003 James Van Sweden (Landscape Series), 2003 March 18; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - March 6, 2003 FY2003 Richard Brown, 2003 March 6; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Monday March 10 FY03 Whistler's Venice, 2003 March 10; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - March 12, 2003 FY2003 Gina Caruso - Songs From the Parlour, 2003 March 12; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - March 19, 2003 FY2003 William Wegman, 2003 March 19; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - March 20, 2003 FY2003 John Walsh - Env. Film Festival, 2003 March 20; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - March 21, 2003 FY2003 Matisse / Picasso trip to New York, 2003 March 21; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - March 24, 2003 FY2003 Rudy Autio, 2003 March 24; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - March 25, 2003 Robin Givhan, 2003 March 25; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - March 26, 2003 FY2003 Ibero-American: Chile, 2003 March 26; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - March 27, 2003 Per Tengstrand, 2003 March 27; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - T735B March 30 FY03 NYC Trip, 2003 March 30; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - 2003 April PPCAL FY2003, Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - April 2 2003 FY2003 Ziva Spanish Dance, 2003 April 2; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Saks Jandel, Circa 2003; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - April 3, 2003 FY2003 Armani at Saks Jandel, 2003 April 3; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - April 8, 2003 I am Madame X, 2003 April 8; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - April 9, 2003 FY2003 Evening at the Embassy of Poland, 2003 April 9; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Aapril 14, 2003 FY2003 Persian Classical Music, 2003 April 14; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Laurie Olin April 15, 2003 Landscape Architecture, 2003 April 15; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - April 21, 2003 FY2003 Michael Kahn, 2003 April 21; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Hillwood 2 April 24, 2003, 2003 April 24; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Contemp April 2728, 2003 April 27-28; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - April 28 FY2003 Progressive Dinner, 2003 April 28; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - April 29, 2003 FY2003 Evening at the Residence of the Moroccan Amb., 2003 April 29; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - April 30, 2003 FY2003 Deborah Brenner - Erica Hall Concert, 2003 April 30; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - 2002 October PPCAL FY2003, Circa 2003; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - October 3, 2002 Cuban Dancers CANCELED, 2002 October 3; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - L684 October 2 FY2003 Dominique Browning, 2003 October 3; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - October 7, 2002 FY2003 Ari Roth, 2002 October 7; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - October 9, 2002 FY2003 Falling Water, 2002 October 9; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - October 10, 2002 FY2003 Hilton Kramer, 2002 October 10; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Songbirds October 67 FY2003, 2002 October 6-7; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - October 16, 2002 FY2003 Beest Cellars Wine Tasting, 2002 October 16; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - October 17, 2002 John Eaton, 2002 October 17; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - October 22, 2002 Home Swell Home, 2002 October 22; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - October 25, 2002 FY2003 MoMA QNS, 2002 October 25; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - October 28, 2002 FY2003 Evelyn Nef, 2002 October 28; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - October 24, 2002 FY2003 Judith Leiber, 2002 October 24; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - 2002 November PPCAL FY2003, Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Canceled, Circa 2003; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - November 6, 2002 FY2003 Grounds for Sculpture Tour, 2002 November 6; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - November 9, 2002 FY2003 Robert McNamara - German Playwrights, 2002 November 9; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - November 11, 2002 FY2003 Steve Ross, 2002 November 11; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - November 13, 2002 FY2003 Bruce Davidson, 2002 November 13; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - November 14, 2002 FY2003 Ibero-American Concert - Uruguay, 2002 November 14; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - November 20, 2002 FY2003 Eric Brace, 2002 November 20; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - November 21, 2002 FY2003 Gypsy Strings, 2002 November 21; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - L705A/L705B November 24 and 25, 2002 FY2003 Embassy of Norway Press Preview at Union Station and Design Panel, 2002 November 24-25; Series 1 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - 2002 July PPCAL FY2003, Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - July 16 Travis Fox - WHNPA Series FY2003 CANCELED, 2002 July 16; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - July 29 Love Letters FY2003 CANCELED, 2002 July 29; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - July 16, 2003 FY2004 Eve at the Embassy of Switzerland, 2003 July 16; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - July 17 FY2003 Jack Valenti, 2002 July 17; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - July 8 FY2003 Andrea Reese - Cirque Jacqueline, 2002 July 8; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - July 12 FY2003 James River Plantation Tour, 2002 July 12; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - July 18 FY2003 Hamish Bowles, 2002 July 18; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - July 22 FY2003 Joseph Holtzman - nest L666, 2002 July 22; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - L555 Robin Givhan Fy2002 July 23, 2001 July 23; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - July 24 FY2003 Matisse Restaurant, 2002 July 24; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - July 25, 2002 FY03 Mexican Cultural Institute, 2002 July 25; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - July 26 FY2003 Art Trip to Philadelphia, 2002 July 26; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - August 2, 2002 FY2003 Art Trip to Philadelphia, 2002 August 2; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - August 1 FY2003 Capitol Tour, 2002 August 1; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - August 22 FY2003 Designing Camelot, 2002 August 22; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - 2002 September PPCAL FY2003, Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - September 18 FY2003 Bobby Van's Steakhouse CANCELED, 2002 September 18; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - September 9 FY2003 Phillip Pearlstein, 2002 September 9; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - September 12 FY2003 Jay Mulvaneyy - Jackie: The Clothes of Camelot, 2002 September 12; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - September 17 FY2003 Photo Safari, 2002 September 17; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - September 13 FY2003 Rachel Harnisch with the Embassy of Switzerland CANCELED, 2002 September 13; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Sept. 23 FY2002 Egyptian Residence T659, 2002 September 23; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Sept. 24 2002 Embassy Walking Tour, 2002 September 24; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - L686A/L686B September 25 and 27, 2002 FY2003 Iranian Film Festival, 2002 September 25,27; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - L682 September 24 FY2003 Chris Madden, 2002 September 24; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - L681 September 26 FY2003 Cecil Stoughton, 2002 September 26; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - L679 September 10 FY2003 Ian Schrager, 2002 September 10; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - FR September 18, 2002 FY2003 AFTA, 2002 September 18; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - July Public Programs Calendar, 2003 July; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Philip Brookman - Robert Frank, 2003 July 9; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Barbara Haber, 2003 July 2003; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Edith Piaf, 2003 July 15; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Charles Guggenheim, 2003 July 17; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - City Museum, 2003 July 22; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Joseph Perna, 2003 July 23; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Eric Denker - Childe Hassam, 2003 July 24; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Andre Leon Talley, 2003 July 28; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Ibero American - Brazil, 2003 July 31; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Public Programs Calendar, 2003 September; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Grounds for Sculpture (Member Tour) Cancelled, 2003 September 18; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Architectural Photo Safaris, 2004 September; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Richard Guy Wilson, 2003 September 10; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Deborah Solomon with Frank Stella, 2003 September 15; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Fallingwater and Kentuck Knob, 2003 September 16; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - 166th Street Embassy Walking Tour, 2003 September 17; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Anna Bergman, 2003 September 22; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Guerrilla Girls, 2003 September 24; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Steve Martin with Deborah Soloman, 2003 September 29; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Ibero American - Spain, 2003 September 30; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Public Programs Calendar, 2003 October; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Nat Chandler Cancelled, 2003 October 5; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Jesse Browner Cancelled, 2003 October 8; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Seward Johnson, 2003 October 9; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Johansen International, 2003 October 12; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Susan Meiselas, 2003 October 14; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Petra Chu - Manet, 2003 October 16; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Barry Hoffman, 2003 October 20; Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - El Greco Trip to NYC, 2003 October 21; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Blandine Rnnou, 2003 October 22; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Brandon Green, 2003 October 26; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - FGI Fashion Retailers, 2003 October 23; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Steve Ross - An American in Paris, 2003 October 27; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Public Programs Calendar, 2003 November; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - John Brookes - Postponed, 2003 Noveember 2; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Storm King, Die Etc. Cancelled, 2003 November; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Manja Temo (Hall Concert) Cancelled, 2003 November 5; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Robin Givhan, 2003 November 4; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Architects Homes, 2003 November 10; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Contemporary Music Forum, 2003 November 10; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Seward Johnson Documentary, 2003 November 13; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Patti Wicks, Keter Betters and Bob Dorough, 2003 November 15; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Salon Dore Concert, 2003 November 16; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Best Cellars, 2003 November 17; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Jeffrey Bilhuber, 2003 November 19; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Robert Prosky, 2003 November 20; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Constitution Museum in Philadelphia, 2003 November 21; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Public Programs Calendar, 2003 December; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Stevie Holladn Cancelled, 2003 December 2; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Russell Versaci Cancelleed, 2003 December 1; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Jim Sanborn and Richard Rhodes, 2003 December 4; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Michael York - Enoch Arden, 2003 December 8; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Swell Holiday, 2003 December 10; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Festive Evening at the Residence of Bulgaria, 2003 December 9; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Laura Coyle on Van Gogh, 2003 December 11; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Holiday Fashion in Philadelphia and NYC, 2003 December 12; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Samuel White - McKim, Mead and White, 2003 December 15; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Dick Katz Trio Cancelled, 2003 December 14; Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Public Programs Calendar, 2004 January; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Irving Sandler Cancelled, 2004 January 21; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Photo Safari, 2004 January 4; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Stanley Hallet, 2004 February 4; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Eternal Egypt at the Walters, 2004 January 16; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Palette Benefit, 2004 January 17; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Dinner at the Embassy of Bahrain, 2004 January 22; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - John Eaton, 2004 January 28; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Dinner at 2941, 2004 January 29; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Public Programs Calendar, 2004 February; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Kojo Nnamdi and Joe Barber, 2004 February 2; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Harlem Collection: Frank Owens and Jeree Wade, 2004 February 3; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Gay Men's Chorus of Washington DC, 2004 February; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Gail Collins, 2004 February 17; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Lithuanian National Day Concert, 2004 February 18; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Chesttee Harrington, 2004 February 19; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Public Programs Calendar, 2004 March; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Barbara Brussell, 2004 March 2; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Leo A. Daly, 2004 March 3; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Dinner at Resideence of Netherlands Ambassador, 2004 March 10; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Friday Morning Music Club, 2004 March 14; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Manet and the Sea/Bus Trip, 2004 March 12; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Theatre Design Panel, 2004 March 15; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Photos to Send/Env. Film Festival, 2004 March 18; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Nina Laden, 2004 March 21; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Contemporary Music Forum, 2004 March 22; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Saudi Arabia, 2004 March 25; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Ziva Spanish Dance, 2004 March 29; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - April Gornik, 2004 March 30; Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - July 2004 Public Program Calendar, 2004 July; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - WHNPA: Karen Ballard, 2004 July 13; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Hillwood, 2004 July 14; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Best Cellars University at the Corcoran, 2004 July; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Charlottsville Bus Trip, 2004 July 16; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - DC Artistry, 2004 July 20; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Ralph Rucci, 2004 July 21; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Letitia Baldrige, 2004 July 28; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Residence of the Ambassador of Iceland, 2004 July 30; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Night Day, 2004 August; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Elizabeth Mahew, 2004 August 2; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Residence of the Ambassador of Colombia, 2004 August 4; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Cana Gioia (With John Andrews) Cancelled, 2004 September 21; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - John McCaslin, 2004 September 13; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Dinner at Le Paradou, 2004 September 14; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - H.R.H. Princess Michael of Kent, 2004 September 10; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Lynda Benglis, 2004 September 20; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Anna Bergman, 2004 September 21; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - DC Architecture/Bus Tour, 2004 September 22; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Guity Adjoodiani - Journey to Iran, 2004 September 27; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Frank Gehry (Eye on Design Series), 2004 September 28; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Night Day, 2004 August; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Peter Bogdanovich, 2004 October 4; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Karim Rashid (Eye on Design Series), 2004 October 5; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 24)